<updateinfo>
<release version="0.55" changelog="September 2016: v0.55
- Packed images into the DLLs, to reduce project clutter.
- Added a brand new, slicker Unfinity Games Updater, that'll be used from now on.
- Updated the Changelog Viewer.  It's now a pop-up modal window inside of the new Updater.
- Deprecated the old method call to the old updater -- if you're using any other Unfinity Games assets, you'll get a warning in the console.  This'll go away automatically when those assets get updated to the newest version.
- Fixed a minor bug regarding checking for whitespace.
- Bulletproofed some potential null-reference-throwing core functions.
- Implemented a new way to cache internal resources.  Performance and loading reliability have been improved!
- Added a new Layout Flip option in the Preferences, allowing for the Options panel to be on the left or right.
- Fixed an issue where method names weren't being added to the hoverable tooltip.
- Added a new options menu button to the Script Creation Wizard.  It's located in the upper right-hand side of the window.
- Added an option to open a dockable version of the Script Creation Wizard. (Located in the new options menu)
- Added an option to open the Unity Preferences. (Located in the new options menu)
- Added an option to reset the Script Creation Wizard's window size. (Located in the new options menu)
- Performance has been improved across the board!
- Other small bugfixes/changes." changelogURL="http://www.unfinitygames.com/interact/threads/utemplate-0-55-released.19/"/>
<release version="0.54" changelog="July 2016: v0.54
- Fixed a few minor bugs.
- Added support for the automatic filling-in of base.Method calls for overridden methods.
- Added a button in the Preferences that links to the Documentation.
- Added the Readme." changelogURL="http://www.unfinitygames.com/interact/threads/utemplate-beta-0-54-released.18/"/>
<release version="0.53" changelog="June 2016: v0.53
- Initial Beta Release" changelogURL=""/>
</updateinfo>
