<updateinfo>
<release version="0.60" changelog="November 2016: v0.60b
- uTemplate is now in stable beta.  Thanks to all the early beta testers!
- Fixed a rare bug with the Unfinity Games Updater where the initial size would be too large if all available assets were installed at once.
- Fixed a case where templates could be stored in the incorrect location, due to bad caching.
- Fixed a case where method file tags could bleed into method name declarations, if no space inserted between them.
- Subdirectories will now be searched properly when checking for installed templates.
- Fixed a case where a space after a [DEFAULT] tag was required for proper parsing.
- Added a new method tag: Unity version.  Tagging a method with this will hide the method if the current Unity version doesn't support it.
- Updated a few of the built-in templates.
- Added a new feature: Downloading Templates.  Templates can now be downloaded from uTemplate's Github repository.
- Added a 'Download New Templates' entry to the Script Creation Wizard's options menu.
- Updated/rewrote how template overrides are calculated.
- Added downloaded templates to the override priority calculations.  Template priority is now Custom > Downloaded > Built-in.
- Added a 'Refresh Window' entry to the Script Creation Wizard's option menu, and made F5 refresh the window.
- Updated the template selection dropdown menu.  It now supports sub-menu sorting, based off of the directories your templates are in.  Great for organizing!
- Added an asterisk to a template's dropdown display name if it's currently overriding another template.
- Added a Shift+Control+T hotkey to open the Script Creation Wizard.
- Extracted the Script Creation Wizard's MenuItem out of the DLL and into a separate file, so its location and hotkey can be changed freely.
- Made some changes so uTemplate works as far back as Unity 4.7.0.
- Added a specific GUI case in the Preset Window for when there's no Presets to display.
- Fixed Create + Attach not working in Unity versions earlier than 5.3.
- Added a preference option allowing verbose logging to be toggled on/off.
- Other small bugfixes/changes." changelogURL="http://www.unfinitygames.com/interact/threads/utemplate-beta-0-60-released.25/"/>
<release version="0.56" changelog="September 2016: v0.56
- Added a new feature: UI Resizing! The preview panel and options panel can now be resized.
- When switching to a dockable window, Keep Open is now enabled by default (so you can dock it!).
- The absolute width of the Preferences GUI has been removed.  It'll now do its best to scale with the size of the Preferences window.
- Changed how method toggle info is stored.  Due to methods potentially having the same name, the entire method signature is now stored to ensure uniqueness.
- Other small bugfixes/changes." changelogURL="http://www.unfinitygames.com/interact/threads/utemplate-beta-0-56-released.20/"/>
<release version="0.55" changelog="September 2016: v0.55
- Packed images into the DLLs, to reduce project clutter.
- Added a brand new, slicker Unfinity Games Updater, that'll be used from now on.
- Updated the Changelog Viewer.  It's now a pop-up modal window inside of the new Updater.
- Deprecated the old method call to the old updater -- if you're using any other Unfinity Games assets, you'll get a warning in the console.  This'll go away automatically when those assets get updated to the newest version.
- Fixed a minor bug regarding checking for whitespace.
- Bulletproofed some potential null-reference-throwing core functions.
- Implemented a new way to cache internal resources.  Performance and loading reliability have been improved!
- Added a new Layout Flip option in the Preferences, allowing for the Options panel to be on the left or right.
- Fixed an issue where method names weren't being added to the hoverable tooltip.
- Added a new options menu button to the Script Creation Wizard.  It's located in the upper right-hand side of the window.
- Added an option to open a dockable version of the Script Creation Wizard. (Located in the new options menu)
- Added an option to open the Unity Preferences. (Located in the new options menu)
- Added an option to reset the Script Creation Wizard's window size. (Located in the new options menu)
- Performance has been improved across the board!
- Other small bugfixes/changes." changelogURL="http://www.unfinitygames.com/interact/threads/utemplate-0-55-released.19/"/>
<release version="0.54" changelog="July 2016: v0.54
- Fixed a few minor bugs.
- Added support for the automatic filling-in of base.Method calls for overridden methods.
- Added a button in the Preferences that links to the Documentation.
- Added the Readme." changelogURL="http://www.unfinitygames.com/interact/threads/utemplate-beta-0-54-released.18/"/>
<release version="0.53" changelog="June 2016: v0.53
- Initial Beta Release" changelogURL=""/>
</updateinfo>
